Finding Aid for the USA for Africa Records LSC.1669
UCLA Library Special Collections
- W.I.D. Rejects
  - O.E.F. with M.F.R. - W.I.D. Senegal - "Income - generation." (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - W.I.D. - General correspondence. (Box 133, Folder 19)